

JOB CHATTATIKUNNU

Frontend Developer

Contact Me

+4915117284649 jobjose89@gmail.com In Der Au 12 Seefeld Hechendorf Munich Munich,Germany

Birth Date

23/July/1993

Other Info

Skills

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, BOOTSTRAP, JQUERY, GIT

Languages

English, Hindi

Interest

Music, Travelling, Driving

Others

web development and design

in

linkedin.com/in/jobjose-a19218110

Summary

My self Job chattatikunnu and i am a citizen of India, currently live in Germany, Munich. I am a frontend web developer with 1.5 year of experience in india and Ukraine and ,The work I do, Working with clients to develop the overall look and design of a website. Writing website code with HTML,CSS JAVASCRIPT BOOTSTRAP Producing, maintaining and modifying websites and user interfaces.

Education

University Of kerala

2014 - 20017

Bachelor Degree In Computer Science

Govt Poly Technic / Keltron

2012 - 2013

Diploma In Computerized Instrumentation

Kerala State Board

2008 - 2010

12th - Science

NSS High School

10th

Experience

Gurvindrar International

2021 - 2022

Junior Frontend Web Developer

G-tec Solutions

2018 - 2019

Tech Support Trainee